https://www.winningdomains.com/legal-privacy-policy/

Legal Disclaimer
We sell generic and descriptive gambling-related domain names. Any issues or conflicts the use of these names may have with the rights of any trademark owners, and/or of any identical and/or similar names are the responsibility of the buyer to determine, through investigation and legal consultation.
* The U.S. Government provides an electronic trademark search function: https://www.uspto.gov/trademark
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy was last modified on June 30, 2018.
This page has been created to inform customers of our privacy policy, regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal
Information we receive from WinningDomains.com customers
Your identity, along with the transactional information, will not be collected, sold or released to anyone. We only obtain information that is necessary to negotiate the sale and transfer of a domain name. When using this site, you are agreeing to the collection and use of your information, in accordance with this limited purpose.
Information Collection and Usage
When inquiring about a domain and/or purchasing a name, you will only be asked to provide your personal information via our chat box, and/or e-mail communication. Your name and email are used initially, for contact purposes, which include responding to domain price inquiries or any general questions, and secondarily, for transferring a domain name. Your personal information (first/last name and email) will not be given or shared with any third party.
Log Data
Finally, like most sites, we collect log data whenever someone visits our site. Log data includes information about the site pages customers visited, the date and time of their visits, and the overall length of time spent on our website.
If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please email info@winningdomains.com.
About Us
WinningDomains.com has been a leading reseller of premium, business domain names since 1999. We provide competitive pricing, excellent customer service, choice of escrow company, and personalized purchase plans, including installment sales via domain holding escrows. Our goal is to assist you in finding the right domain for your business.
We sold:
AboveItAll.comAccountables.comAccountingWise.comAccountOnIt.comAcuScan.comAllToWin.comBabyAlexa.comBabyAlexandra.comBabyBenjamin.comBabyBookmark.comBabyBrooklyn.comBabyChan.comBabyDiego.comBabyEd.comBabyElle.comBabyFaith.comBabyItsYou.comBabyJake.comBabyJames.comBabyJesus.orgBabyJordan.comBabyKen.comBabyLexi.comBabyMia.comBabyMike.comBabyVi.comBabyZen.comBestReturn.comBetAll.comBetEdge.comBetFunds.comBetOnIt.comBetPlay.netBetSeven.comBetTicket.comBettingCredits.comBettingIQ.comCastleCasino.comCoastRealtors.comCoastRentals.comCPAServices.comDentalNet.comDentalWise.comDiaperWise.comDigitalDice.comDimeBet.comDreamWinner.comDreamWinners.comE1031.comEHorseRacing.comExpectToWin.comFantasyVentures.comFootballTips.comFunBet.comFunWise.comGamingExperts.comGamingTime.comGreatBets.comHearingWise.comHoneydew.netHorseAdvisor.comHorseAnalytics.comHorseClass.comHorseIQ.comHorseWise.comInstaBet.comInstaYoga.comInTheClutch.comISellProperty.comIWinBets.comKeepMore.comKingOdds.comLABetting.comLiveByTheBeach.comLuckyHit.comLuckyTips.comLuxePicks.comMedicalAdvocates.comNeonVegas.comNetHoops.comNeuroWise.comOddsEdge.comOddsKing.comOnlineLaw.netOnTheStrip.comPetHelp.comPlanWisely.comPlayerMall.comPlayHorses.comPlayOnIt.comPlayWise.comPokerFitness.comPokerMatrix.comRacingDomain.comRacingEdge.comRacingInsider.comRacingPicks.comRawSun.comRiverPoker.comRSINet.comRunItUp.comSafeCasinos.comScience101.comSeeBetter.comSelectBets.comSportsBettingStars.comSportsGambler.comSportsPicksDaily.comSpotWin.comStableCash.comStrokeWise.comTaxCures.comTaxEdge.comTaxesNow.comTaxesPlus.comTaxFix.comTaxHotline.comTaxReducer.comTaxRelief.netThatsWhatIMean.comTripleCrownWinners.comTurfBet.comTurfBet.netTurfBets.comTurfWinners.comUBingo.comWeEducate.comWellBred.comWinCircle.comWinEdge.comWinHearts.comWinnersWeekly.comWinnerX.comWinningPlay.comWinningPro.comWinningPros.comWinOdds.comWinRate.comWinWager.comWinYourDream.comWinYourDreams.comWireToWire.comWireWise.comWiseGamingWiseStrategy.comWPSNet.comXHorse.comYogaEdge.com
Looking for a gambling-related domain?
© 1999-2020 Winning Domains. All rights reserved.
